Who Says
压制:随Feng
谁说
歌手
Selena Gomez
Wouldn't wanna be anybody else, hey
我才不要做任何人的影子呢
You made my insecure
你让我没安全感
To me I wasn't good enough
你告诉我我不够好
But who are you to judge
可是你有什么资格批评我呢
When you're diamond in the rough
你自己也是未经打磨的钻石
Am sure you got some things
我知道你一定有才华的
You like to change about yourself
你会想改变自己
but when it comes to me
不过如果你问我
I wouldn't want to be anybody else
我不想作除了自己的任何人
Nananana, nananana
I'm no beauty queen, I'm just beautiful me
我不是美丽女皇 我只是美丽的我
Nananana, nananana
You got every right to a beautiful life
你拥有每个权利去活得漂亮
Come on
继续向前
Who says
谁说
Who says you're not perfect
谁说你不完美
who says you're not worth it
谁说你不值得
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
谁说只有你在伤心
Trust me that's the price of beauty
相信我这就是美丽的代价
Who says you're not pretty
谁说你不漂亮
who says you're not beautiful
谁说你不美丽
Who says
谁说
It's such a funny thing
这真的很有趣
How nothing's funny when it's you
你告诉他们你是什麼意思
You tell me what you need
你告诉我你需要什么
But it can widen out the the truth
不过他们一直扭曲事实
It's like a work of art
就像一件艺术品
But never get to see the lights
永远无法面世
Keep you beneath the stars
让你一直在星辰下
won't let you touch the sky
不让你触碰天空
Nananana, nananan
I'm no beauty queen, I'm just beautiful me
我不是美丽女皇 我只是美丽的我
Nananana, nananana
You got every right to a beautiful night
你拥有每个权利去活得漂亮
Come on
继续向前
Who says
谁说
Who says you're not perfect
谁说你不完美
who says you're not worth it
谁说你不值得
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
谁说只有你在伤心
Trust me that's the price of beauty
相信我 这就是美丽的代价
Who says you're not pretty
谁说你不漂亮
who says you're not beautiful
谁说你不美丽
Who says
谁说
Who say you're not star potential
谁说你没有巨星潜质
who says you're presidential
谁说你没有当总统的潜能
Who says you can't be in movies
谁说你不能拍电影
listen to me, listen to me
听我说 听我说
Who says you don't pass a test
谁说你不会及格
who says you can't be the best
谁说你不能做最好的
who said, who said
谁说过  谁说过
Would you tell me who said that, yeah
你会告诉我谁说过吗
Who says
谁说
Who says you're not perfect
谁说你不完美
who says you're not worth it
谁说你不值得
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
谁说只有你在伤心
Trust me that's the price of beauty
相信我这就是美丽的代价
Who says you're not pretty
谁说你不漂亮
who says you're not beautiful
Who says
谁说
Who says you're not perfect
谁说你不完美
who says you're not worth it
谁说你不值得
who says you're the only one that's hurting
谁说只有你在伤心
Trust me that's the price of beauty
相信我这就是美丽的代价
Who says you're not pretty
谁说你不漂亮
who says you're not beautiful
Who says
谁说
压制:随Feng